hey Knuckles hurry up in the bathroom we
want to play the game before we gotta go
home
I'm sorry Sonic really I am it's just
that the critic from lunch is really
making me poop maybe we should go in the
dungeon without him I'm sure the three
of us could do it if we tried shut up
you strawberry pink [ __ ] your are our
only life wizard and I'm an ice wizard
we focus too heavily on defense and
Manic would be the only attacker what if
his insane Bowl backfires we would be
[ __ ]
Nux has to be there or we aren't going
okay I see your point
I don't agree man I can't believe
Malastare is doing all of this just to
bring back Sylvia who could have ever
seen this coming yeah I know I thought
he was gay you guys ready a cake on
Malastare adopt dragon spiral this fight
is finally coming to an end
sure thing oh by the way where is your
great-grandfather I haven't seen him all
day
what the hell does that even matter you
know I really thought you guys were
going to compliment me on my new costume
but if you must know he's up in the
attic I don't have any clue what he does
up there but he tells me you're not
allowed to go in
[Music]
beautiful
I can't wait to upload this to
deviantART oh that reminds me I gotta
check to see if anyone left a review on
my light Excel fanfic oh boy it took two
months but I finally got a review I'm so
excited to read what it says oh no
that's so mean
why why would somebody do this seed I
know carry on okay da da da O'Donnell
Mimi dhakini not on call Narnia Sunday
to go anywhere or any order in a coconut
on a cheeky cote notice enemy toaster
toes under ship honest you know g7 take
and iran denies air
[Music]
they just start to chase it huh what is
this
oh goodness is this this is a ninja star
but that could only mean no it cannot be
I knew it
it's the Yakuza you think you can take
me huh I'm Athair great sage um via
kidness I won't go down without a fight
get the hell out of my house you change
on Chinese son of a [ __ ] kids run get
out of the house there's a [ __ ] ninja
in the Attic
where the helm are you guys going what
about my granddad you heard what he said
Knuckles there's an engine up there you
granddad's [ __ ] dead come on sips its
juice and jam time what you're leaving
fine if you won't help him then I win
great grandfather are you okay just hang
on I'm coming to save you no Knuckles
you can't turn back while you still can
ordinal me me Loki knee not alcohol
sheep on us you know gene synaptic and I
ran and I say please don't hurt him
he's just an innocent boy he has nothing
to do with this nany only a Sunday to
call anywhere or any order in a coconut
and I Ziggy called a notice enemy to
stare oh okay go kill him then I don't
want to die please kill him
tall Zenda shape honest you know ginseng
on taking iran denies there
see they know guardian i'll cut out a
paper bomb what you said I wouldn't be
harmed you lied to me
you won't get away with this
you [ __ ] Chinese [ __ ] I'll shove
chopsticks up your ass
[Music]
[ __ ] did you guys see that
then enjoys flying away I can't believe
Knuckles is [ __ ] dead let's go home
and tell mom to lock the windows we
don't want that ninja flying into our
house next